









# **SUMMARY**

Arun

**JOURNALIST** 

A Multi-talented and Multi-task immensely creative journalist with a commitment to highquality research and writing. Proven history of achievement in the field of broadcast media industry with more than 07 years of professional experience.

Dedication to sound investigative research methods and a strong desire to know the truth of the matter. Excellent reporting, interviewing and presenting skills with writing techniques. Experience writing and reporting across a variety of platforms, including print, television, and online social media. Social engagement with the community, friendliness and communication skills are a trademark.

# **SKILLS**

- Leadership
- Public Speaking
- Time Management
- All The Works Related To Media
- Writing
- Interviewing
- Organize And Manage Community Awareness Activities
- Social Works
- · Strong Decision Maker

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Content Consultant**

World Times Mar 2016 - Present

 Overall in-charge in maintaining the quality of the news content. conduct training sessions to news reporters and news editors.

#### Deputy Editor

My News Online Mar 2019 - Oct 2019

Manage the news content and publish the news articles.

#### **News Caster**

Verizon Communications Feb 2009 - Mar 2016

- All the works related to the news.
- Shoot news events, video editing, narrations, and voice-overs.
- Worked in TVM Atoll bureaus. Visited all the atolls and islands throughout the Maldives.
- · Meet all the Community groups and NGO's.
- Organize and participate in the community awareness programs and in collaboration with the community groups and other stakeholders.

## **Company Secretary**

Kweichow Moutai Apr 2015 - Present

Manage and run the company under the instruction of the Managing Director.

## **Data Entry**

Citigroup Sep 2007 - Nov 2009

- Collect Data for Consumer Price Index CPI.
- Enter the data and do all the works related to Monthly and annual inflation report of the country.
- · Write an inflation report by using the data.
- Visit the different atolls and islands to survey the living standards and collect samples.

## **EDUCATION**

## Masters of Arts Journalism and Media Communication

New York Institute of Technology Present

As an accomplishment of Premaster program November 2019, I was offered to complete a Masters Degree in Arts Journalism and Media Communication by 2020, starting on Feb 2020 and will be completed in November 2020.

Pre-Masters in Arts Journalism and Media Communications

The University of Texas at Dallas Jul 2019 - Nov 2019

Diploma in Journalism

Pace University Feb 2011 - Nov 2012

Certificate in Broadcast Journalism

Pace University Nov 2008 - Feb 2009

**LANGUAGES** 

**English** 

Chines

French

German

• • • • •

**HOBBIES** 

**Reading Books** 

Playing Foot Ball

Travelling

Social works

Teaching or Conduct Short Training

programs